hr.am 2019-06-23

# HR.am - Privacy Policy

HR.AM ( HR.AM ," "We," "Our" or "Us") is committed to respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement") applies to information that We collect from you via this Web site ("Web Site" or "Site"), located at [http://hr.am](http://hr.am/), and from your use of any Services that We provide via the Site. "Services" means services provided by or on this Site, the Site itself, and any other services as defined in the Terms of Use for this Site, which are incorporated by reference. This Privacy Statement does not apply to information that We may collect by other methods.

Please read this Privacy Statement carefully, as it will tell you what information We collect about you and your use of Our Services, how We collect, use, share, and protect that information, and the choices you have about how We use and share such information. By using Our Site or Services, you agree that you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Statement and to all other relevant terms, including Our Terms of Use for this Site. 

## Information We Collect

We have access to the following categories of information about you and your use of Our Services. Only some of this information identifies you directly, but some information that does not identify you directly could be used to make inferences about you and, if combined with other information, might be capable of identifying you.

## Information That You Provide

**Personally Identifiable Information.** "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that could be used to identify or contact you and includes data such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and biographical information. There may be many other kinds of Personally Identifiable Information, the foregoing list is provided by example only.

**Site Registration.** You may browse jobs on this Site without registering. To apply for a job, make your resume available for future jobs, and/or you must register for a new User Account. The new User Account set up requires an e-mail address and password. You must then set up a Profile where you are required to provide the following Personally Identifiable Information: first name, last name, country, home phone number and e-mail. You may also submit additional information, such as your employment and educational history, to provide a more complete Profile. You have the opportunity at any time to update your Personally Identifiable Information contained in your Profile. 

## How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We use information about your activities and use of Our Services gathered in the manners described above to monitor user traffic patterns, analyze what Our users prefer so that We can improve Our Services, and potentially provide you with information about jobs that may be of interest to you.

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information.** We will use the Personally Identifiable Information you give Us to (1) send you a confirmation e-mail if you register with Our Site, (2) contact you if We need more information related to your application, Profile, or job search, (3) process a job application made by you, (4) respond to questions from you, (5) possibly contact you about jobs that may be of interest to you; and/or (6) possibly update you about changes affecting the Site, Our Services, or your User Account. The information you provide will also be accessible to companies We contract with that are located in countries around the world to assist with the Services such as recruitment process vendors and recruiters.

We reserve the right to contact you regarding your User Account, changes to our Site or related terms, and any other matter that might affect you or Our Services. We may combine the Personally Identifiable Information from your User Account and/or Profile with other information that we otherwise obtain, including information you provide to Us (such as by mail, fax, or phone) or authorize Us to obtain, and information from third parties. We use your User Account and/or Profile information and resume to combine with employment applications stored in other locations at our facilities to perform background verifications with third party vendors.

If you are offered and accept a position with Us, some of the information you provide through this Site and Our Services will be transferred into Our internal human resources and related. By using Our Site and Services, you agree to such a transfer and use of your information. 

## Your Privacy Choices

When you use this Site, you have the following choices about the information you provide.

**Accept/Reject Cookies.** Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies, but if you reject Our cookies, certain functions and conveniences of Our Site may not work properly. Cookies and similar technologies are how We ensure that We can promptly retrieve and deliver information to you when you use Our Site.

**Access, Correct, Update, or Delete* Personally Identifiable Information.**  
You are responsible for maintaining and updating the information in your Profile to keep it current. You may access, correct or update Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to Our Site at any time by logging in to your Profile, subject to certain restrictions imposed by applicable law. You may also request deletion of your User Account by sending an e-mail to info@hr.am. Where required by applicable law, We will notify you if We cannot accommodate such requests to correct, update or delete information, and provide an explanation as to why We cannot do so. 

## Changes in Our Privacy Statement

We will only use your Personally Identifiable Information in the manner described in the Privacy Statement in effect when you provided the information. However, We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Statement, the Terms of Use, and other related terms at any time by posting revisions to this Site. All such changes will be effective when posted, and your use of Our Site or any of Our Services thereafter will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes. Accordingly, you should review the Privacy Statement for this Site each time you visit or log in to this Site. In the event We make any material change to this Privacy Statement that alters the use of your Personally Identifiable Information, we will notify you of such change by email, and you will have the opportunity to have that information deleted in accordance with the Deletion Policy set forth above.

## Questions

If you have any questions about these Terms of Use, please send Us an e-mail at [info@hr.am](mailto:info@hr.am).
